[{"answer": "Never.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love before you met Karen?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "Never?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Let's just make it chummy, aren't we?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "It seems like a crazy period as this election really hits off.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "You know, I'm a slow and steady kind of guy.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "As a matter of fact he did, you know, shortly -- shortly afterwards, yesterday afternoon.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Has Mitt Romney called you and congratulated you about winning Iowa?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "It's as -- as I said in New Hampshire, and -- and also in Iowa, game on.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "So this gets interesting, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "-- I think that's a pretty good analysis of the race.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "-- the race?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "-- that you were the guy with the big ideas.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "It is a little bit confounding that here's a group that was this -- the -- the key -- absolutely the key for the Republicans to win in 2008.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Why has such an incredibly aggressive, fast-moving, seemingly formidable movement dissipated to the extent that it has?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "I certainly make that case, that they're borne out of real convictions and I've tried to reflect those convictions in every aspect of my life.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Do you think your trump card is that you have flip- flopped the least and that you are -- you are -- whether people agree with you or not, you've been the most true to your principles?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean it inspires you to realize the sacrifice that people make and make today.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "-- the war generation, weren't they?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "It would have been a very hard decision.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "If you'd been president after 9/11, would you have gone to war in Iraq, knowing everything you know now?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Based on the information I had at the time, I think we made the right decision.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "So what's the answer?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Yes, it's hard to -- it's hard to go back and Monday morning quarterbacking.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "But what about everything you know now?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "We left on a cliffhanger there, where you were mulling over the nuances of, with all the evidence we now have, would you have gone to war in Iraq?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "The mission was partially finished.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Do you think the mission was finished?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "If you become president in November, would you put American troops back into Iraq?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "The genie is out of the bottle and you have to deal with the situation as it is.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "So, the genie is out of the bottle?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Would you be prepared to put boots on the ground in Iran?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "In fact, I've laid out a pretty clear road map, if you will, as to the things that I think we need to do, and I have stopped short of saying we need to put boots on the ground.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "How you would you do it?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Absolutely not hesitate to do --", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "You wouldn't hesitate to bomb Iran if you had to?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "ANTORUM: That I felt that they were on the precipice of, you know, actually being in a position to produce that nuclear weapon.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "What would it take to trigger that, do you think?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "It would because once that weapon is weaponized and completed and exploded, then we have a situation where the world has changed.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "And just being on the cusp of being able to produce it, you think would be enough to trigger an attack?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "You know, again, my feeling on that is that we, number one, acted indecisively, we acted unwisely, we acted at the behest of international bodies without a national security interest in our -- and I would not engaged.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Gadhafi taken out with allied help?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, let's find -- well, certainly Gadhafi is gone.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Didn't it?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I would only act using the American military if there is a national security interest to our country was threatened.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "So, you -- by the process of elimination, you would have kept Gadhafi in power?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "I'm not sure the dirty work wouldn't be rather dirty as opposed to what we do, which is not dirty work, which is stand up and -- for human rights and stand up for liberty and for the opportunity of people to have political and economic freedom.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "So would be happy to say China, as its military power increases, to start doing some of the dirty work, perhaps, at being the global police force?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "I've -- I served with him for two years.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "-- personally?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "-- from a professional point of view.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well, I think he has a fundamental different view of what -- what makes America a great country.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "What's your main criticism of him as president?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "His view is that the stronger the government is and the more things that I can do for its people, the better this country is going to be.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "What do you think his view is?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "My view is the less the government can do and the more freedom and opportunity you give people, that trusting people and free people and free enterprise -- that America has built the greatest country in the history of the world.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "And what's your view?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "No, you know, marriage is an institution that existed before governments existed.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Given your stance on gay marriage, for example, could you see any circumstances where you might change that in a way that you hardened your position on an issue like abortion, could you see yourself potentially softening your position on gay marriage?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Well, it's a law.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "So when you say you respect their rights, isn't their legal right in New York now to get married?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "I would change the law to make a uniform definition of marriage in this country, because I think -- like the uniform definition for life --", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Would you change the law?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Well, again, I would reinstitute the traditional marriage as the best --", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "You would make it illegal to get married?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "All I would say is that marriage has been voted on 32 times in this country in 32 states, from Maine to California and 32 times the people of this country have said that marriage is between a man and a woman and the public should have a say about this.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Are you going to try to make it illegal for gay people to get married?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Life.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Why was that?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "I would do what every father must do, is to try to counsel your daughter to do the right thing.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "And was pregnant and was begging you to let her have an abortion, would you really be able to look her in the eye and say, no, as her father?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Well, you can make the argument that if she doesn't have this baby, if she kills her child, that that, too, could ruin her life.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "And they are looking at their daughter ,saying, how can I deal with this, because if I make her have this baby, isn't it going to just ruin her life?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "How do you equate that with supporting the death penalty, given there are so many people who actually are completely innocent?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Well, you can --", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "But we can't be, can we?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "I think a lot of it is just a real focus on faith and family.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "How have you managed to do this, and stay so united, so close?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "At the law firm.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "How did you two meet?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "He was so funny the night we met.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "What was it you saw in Rick?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I didn't have --", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "It couldn't have been the sweater?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "That he's not nice.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "And, Karen, what do you think is the biggest misconception about your husband?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "-- become something different?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I think, yes, that's my personal belief.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "But you think people should lay off him on this one?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "And he said -- he said, I'm not going away.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "What was he singing?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I was.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "What were you singing, do you remember?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "(Inaudible).", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "This is going to ruin everything?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Has it been a positive thing?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "We try not to read the news.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "How do you feel when the old man gets attacked?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "Yes, just ignore it.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "The barroom brawls, you know, if you hear someone dissing Santorum?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Oh, you ignore it?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "Well, it's been really busy, but it's been quite an experience.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Sarah, how do you feel?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "So cute, our two younger boys who are not here, they said, \"Dad, you can't run for president because you won't be able to coach Little League baseball.\"", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "For so many reasons.", "docId": "120120pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "In a simple, short way, why would your husband make a good president?", "qSentId": 699}]